all right I'm going to play next a short
video from Anna Pereira in active
inference Institute research
[Music]
fellow hey an A Prayer
here I was disappointed uh that there
was an irresolvable conflict uh during
the time of the Symposium but wanted to
share uh or contribute um a small update
none
L for those of you um who haven't had a
chance to hear from me before um we've
been looking at accelerating and
disseminating active inference for the
Humanities uh we're actually just
starting to call it
aih uh and we continue to make progress
um and quietly incubate in the
background we're not really at a point
to do um a large more solid update uh
but we wanted to quickly say hello and
and say that we are incubating uh we
continue to be available uh for
collaborations or
conversations um others find
useful uh and also to provide an update
that uh we've been really grateful for
the opportunity to incubate within the
larger aii
structure um this has provided several
mutualistic
affordances um has been a really great
um construct within the the larger aii
uh
space so we look forward to being in
touch uh at Future conferences and
symposiums and available for
conversations um in the meantime uh
wishing you a great Symposium and uh be
well
all right